toriavey.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy - ToriAvey.com Cares About Your Privacy

**ToriAvey.com** is committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This privacy policy tells you about the information we collect on our website and how we use that information. By using ToriAvey.com, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy policy, which may be modified from time to time by us.  Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide via the Website or through other official contact with us remains subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms of Use and/or other stated policies.

 **Information We Collect:**

The information we gather falls into two categories: (1) information you supply when you register to receive emails or comment on the website, and (2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our site.

 **Personally Identifying Information**

In operating the Site, ToriAvey.com may include registration, comment forms, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, e-mail addresses, and other contact information.

 **Tracking Information**

 **Cookies.** From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Web site. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on our website other than cookies. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Web site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended. ToriAvey.com permits third party advertisers to provide advertisements to you through the Web Site. Such advertisers may download cookies onto your computer, which would enable them to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. As a result, the advertising network would have the ability to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe would be of most interest to you. ToriAvey.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by third party advertisers.

 **Click Tracking.** As is true of most websites, ToriAvey.com gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the site and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Except as noted herein, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information.

 **IP Addresses.** Each user’s IP address is logged with each visit and each action performed on ToriAvey.com. This information is never provided to the third parties, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, and is logged only for a temporary period of time. IP address information is linked to personal information and may be used in an effort to block a “banned” user from accessing the Site.

 **Advertising.** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. ToriAvey.com DOES NOT provide any personal account information to such advertisers. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

 **Participation on a Public Website**

You should be aware that any personal information you submit on ToriAvey.com in the comments may be read, collected, or used by other users of this Site, including anonymous visitors.

 **Rights with Respect to Your Personal Data**

If you are located in the European Economic Area, you have the following rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) with respect to information we collect that, alone or in combination with other information we collect, can be used to identify you (such information being “personal data”):

 **Right to Information Regarding the Processing of Your Personal Data.** You have the right to obtain the following information:

  * confirmation of whether and where we are processing your personal data;
  * information about the purpose of the processing of your personal data;
  * information about the categories of personal data being processed;
  * information about the existence of, and an explanation of the logic involved in, any automated processing of your personal data that has a significant effect on you;
  * information about the categories of recipients with whom your personal data may be shared; and
  * information about the period for which your personal data will be stored or the criteria used to determine that period.

 **Right to Access to Your Personal Data.**  You may request a copy of your personal data that we, or our third-party processors, collect and maintain. Similarly, you have the right to, when technically feasible, have your personal data transferred to another entity to determine the purpose and means of processing your personal data.

 **Right to Have Errors Corrected**.  You have the right to rectification of inaccurate personal data.  If you notify us that any of your personal data is inaccurate or incomplete, we have the responsibility to, either directly or our third-party processors, ensure that such personal data is erased or corrected.

 **Right to Have Personal Data Erased or Processing Restricted.** Your name and email address are retained until you unsubscribe or until we erase it, whichever occurs first. Any other personal data that is collected during your site visit is retained until you request we erase it or after 26 months, whichever occurs first. You have the right to have your personal data erased when (i) the personal data is no longer needed for its original purpose and no new lawful purpose exists; (ii) the personal data is being processed based solely on your consent and you withdraw your consent; or (iii) the personal data is being processed unlawfully.  Similarly, you have the right to limit our use of your personal data when (i) the personal data is no longer needed for its original purpose, but we still need to maintain the personal data to establish, exercise, or defend legal rights; (ii) the personal data is being processed unlawfully; or (iii) the accuracy of the personal data is contested, but then our use of the personal data is restricted for only so long as it takes to verify the accuracy of the personal data.

 **Right to Object to Processing of Your Personal Data.** You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data if the basis for that processing is (a) public interest; or (b) our own legitimate interests in doing so.  Additionally, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data for the purpose of direct marketing or statistical purposes.

 **Right to Lodge a Complaint with a Supervising Authority.   **You have the right to lodge a complaint concerning the processing of your personal data with your country’s independent public authority designated to act as its data protection “supervising authority” under the GDPR.

 **Right to Withdraw Consent to the Processing of Your Personal Data.**   You have the right to refuse to consent to, and to withdraw your consent to, the processing of your personal data.  To the extent we rely on your consent to collect and store your personal data, when you withdraw such consent we must cease collection and retention of such personal data.  Note, however, we do not require your consent to collect or otherwise process your personal information if (a) such information is not personal data or (b) such information is personal data and we have another lawful basis for processing the personal information (for instance, the information is needed to enter into or preform under a contract with you).

Responses to your requests to us regarding your personal data will be provided free of charge (including copies of materials), except that we may charge a reasonable fee for any repetitive requests, manifestly unfounded or excessive requests, or further copies.  Similarly, we may refuse to act upon requests that are manifestly unfounded or excessive.

 **How Your Information Will Be Used:**

 **Personal Information** We may use your personal account information to operate, maintain, customize and personalize your experience with ToriAvey.com based on your individual usage habits, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our site’s content, layout and the website. We also use the information we collect about you to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our Terms of Service Agreement. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify your identity, to check your qualifications, or to follow up with transactions initiated on the site. We may also use your contact information to inform you of any changes to ToriAvey.com, or to send you additional information about ToriAvey.com.

 **Anonymous Information** We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

 **Use of Cookies** We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

 **Disclosure of Personal Information** We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ToriAvey.com, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of ToriAvey.com or the users of this site, or (3) act under circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of this site.

 **Security**

ToriAvey.com has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

Credit Card Information.

We may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card (“Credit Card Information”) when you place an order with us. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to us, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. We will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to Third Parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction.

 **Disputes**

If you have any concerns or claims with respect to our data handling practices, please contact us first. We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding our use and disclosure of your Individual Information. If your complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through our internal process, or if we do not adequately respond to your question, you agree to resolve your dispute through arbitration. If arbitration is necessary, it will be conducted by telephone and email, and if it must be done in person, it will be conducted in Los Angeles, California. The arbitration will be conducted by one arbitrator member of JAMS, and under the rules of commercial arbitration of JAMS or as agreed between you and the Company. Both parties will bear equally the cost of arbitration (exclusive of legal fees and expenses). All decisions of the arbitrator will be final and binding on both parties and enforceable in any court of competent jurisdiction. For additional information you may contact www.jamsadr.com.

 **Limitation of Liability**

We exercise reasonable efforts to safeguard the security and confidentiality of your personal information; however, transmissions protected by industry standard technology and administered by humans cannot be guaranteed to be secure. We will not be liable for unauthorized disclosure of personal information that occurs through no fault of our own including, but not limited to, errors in transmission, access to your account by anyone, uses of your Member ID and password by a third party, your failure to comply with your security obligations, and the unauthorized acts of our employees.

 **Comments**

ToriAvey.com may include interactive forms such as comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Third Party Websites**

ToriAvey.com may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

 **Children Under 16:**

We care about protecting the privacy of children. We won’t knowingly allow anyone under 16 to provide us any personally identifying information. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. If you’re under 16, please do not provide us with any personally identifying information (such as your name, your email address or your phone number).  We have designed this policy in order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). You may read more about COPPA at [http://www.coppa.org](http://www.coppa.org/). If you become aware that your child, a Minor, has provided us with personal information without your consent, you should contact us immediately.

 **Additional Terms**

California User Consumer Rights. In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with the California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov. Sec. 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, grants residents of the State of California the right to request from a business with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, once a year, certain information with respect to the types of personal information that the business shares with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To exercise your rights, you may make one request each year by contacting us as set forth in the How to Contact Us section.

 **Website Provider – Host Information**

Cloudways Ltd. (C 55975)  
52 Springvale Pope Pius XII Street  
Mosta, Malta

You can find the Cloudways Privacy Policy [here](https://www.cloudways.com/en/terms.php#privacy).

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this policy, or our practices related to this site, [contact us here](mailto:info%40toriavey%2ecom?subject=ToriAvey%2ecom%20Inquiry).

 **Updates and Changes**

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this privacy policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on ToriAvey.com and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site. It is your responsibility to review this privacy policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.

 _This policy was last updated on May 23, 2018._

 _©   _ToriAvey, LLC.  All rights reserved.
